// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" SMALL\" ",
    answer: "BIG",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAST",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" SLOW\" ",
    answer: "FAST",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAST",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" HAPPY\" ",
    answer: "SAD",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAST",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" SHORT\" ",
    answer: "TALL",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAST",
      "TALL"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" THIN\" ",
    answer: "FAT",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAT",
      "OLD"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Find opposite word of \" YOUNG\" ",
    answer: "OLD",
    options: [
      "SAD",
      "BIG",
      "FAT",
      "OLD"
    ]
  }
  /*
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "which word is wrong ",
    answer: "ordq",
    options: [
      "text",
      "ordq",
      "find",
      "part"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'r' ",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "V",
      "R",
      "W",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the letter 'C'",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "A",
      "Y",
      "C",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Find the letter 'X'",
    answer: "X",
    options: [
      "V",
      "X",
      "A",
      "U"
    ]
  }
  */
];
